Oh, hey!
哦，嘿！
How was your audition?
你的試鏡怎麼樣？
I'm sorry, do I know you?
對不起，我認識你嗎？
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Nothing, I'm just practicing blowing you off, because
沒什麼，我只是練習把你吹走，因為
I'm going to be a big movie star!
我要成為大電影明星！
You got it?
你明白了嗎？
Well, no, not yet, but the audition went
嗯，不，還沒有，但是試鏡進行了
really good.
真的很好。
What was it for?
是做什麼用的？
Oh, it's this big budget period movie about
哦，這是一部大預算時期的電影
these three Italian brothers who come to America
來到美國的這三個義大利兄弟
around the turn of the century.
大約在世紀之交。
It's really classy.
這真的很優雅。
And the director is supposed to be the
而且導演應該是
next, next Martin Scorsese.
接下來是馬丁·史柯西斯。
The next, next?
下一個，下一個？
Yeah, there's this guy from Chicago who's supposed
是的，有一個來自芝加哥的人應該
to be the next Martin Scorsese, but then
成為下一個馬丁·史柯西斯，但隨後
this guy's right after him.
這傢伙就在追他。
Hello?
你好？
Joey, it's Estelle!
喬伊，是埃斯特爾！
I just talked to the casting people, they
我剛剛和選角人員談過，他們
loved you!
愛你！
They loved me?
他們愛我嗎？
Yeah, and they want to see you again
是的，他們想再見到你
tomorrow.
明天。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
It's just one thing.
這只是一件事。
Do you have a problem with full frontal
你有全額的問題嗎
nudity?
裸露？
Are you kidding me?
你在開玩笑吧？
I never read the movie without it!
沒有它我就從來沒有看過這部電影！
Oh.
哦。
Okay, let me call you back.
好的，我回你電話。
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
They want me to be totally naked in
他們希望我完全赤裸
the movie.
電影。
Wow!
哇！
I know.
我知道。
My grandmother's gonna see this.
我祖母會看到這個。
Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
奶奶得排隊了。
Come on.
快點。
The wedding
婚禮
is
是
so close, are you getting nervous?
這麼近，你緊張嗎？
Yeah, but a part of me also can't
是的，但我的一部分也做不到
wait till it's over.
等到結束。
Chandler and I have this pact not to
錢德勒和我有這個協議，不
have sex again until the wedding.
再次發生性行為直到婚禮。
A no-sex pact, huh?
一個無性契約，對吧？
I actually have one of those going on
我實際上正在進行其中之一
with every woman in America.
與美國的每一位女性。
Hey, baby, will you give me a hand?
嘿，寶貝，你願意幫我一把嗎？
I gotta make up the guest bedroom.
我得收拾一下客房。
Hey, cousin Cassie's coming to stay with us
嘿，卡西表弟要來跟我們住
for a few days.
幾天了。
Cassie?
卡西？
I haven't seen her in, like, forever.
我好像永遠都沒見過她了。
I wonder if she still carries that Barbie
我想知道她是否還帶著那個芭比娃娃
everywhere she goes.
無論她去哪裡。
Ross, she's 25 years old.
羅斯，她25歲了。
So what?
所以呢？
I still have...
我還有...
No, you're probably right.
不，你可能是對的。
Hi.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, Pheebs, can I talk to you over
嘿，菲比，我可以跟你談談嗎
here for a second?
在這裡等一下嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Subtle, guys.
微妙，夥計們。
What?
什麼？
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
我知道你正在籌劃我的驚喜新娘送客派對。
Okay, well, don't ruin it.
好吧，別毀了它。
Just play along, at least.
至少，一起玩吧。
Okay, sorry.
好吧，抱歉。
Oh, my God, we have to throw her
哦，天哪，我們必須丟掉她
a shower?
淋浴？
Hey, what'd you decide to do about the
嘿，你決定做什麼？
movie?
電影？
I don't know.
我不知道。
It's not like it's porn.
這不像是色情片。
This is a serious, legitimate movie, you know?
這是一部嚴肅、合法的電影，你知道嗎？
And the nudity is really important to the
裸體對於
story.
故事。
That's what you say about porn.
這就是你所說的色情內容。
You're right.
你說得對。
Maybe I shouldn't even go on the call
也許我甚至不應該去打電話
back.
後退。
No, no, you should.
不，不，你應該。
A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
很多主要演員都拍裸體戲。
I mean, the chance to star in a
我的意思是，有機會主演一部
movie comes with the nudity.
電影伴隨著裸體。
Come on.
快點。
Well, that's true.
嗯，確實如此。
And I am only naked in one scene.
而且我只在一個場景中赤身裸體。
Plus, it sounds really great.
另外，聽起來真的很棒。
My character's Catholic, and he falls in love
我的角色是天主教徒，他墜入愛河
with this Jewish girl.
和這個猶太女孩。
We run away together and get caught in
我們一起逃跑然後被抓住
this big rainstorm.
這場大暴雨。
So we go into this barn and undress
所以我們走進這個穀倉脫掉衣服
each other and hold each other.
彼此並擁抱彼此。
It's really sweet and tender.
真的是又甜又嫩。
Plus, everyone's going to see your thing.
另外，每個人都會看到你的東西。
When can we have this shower?
我們什麼時候可以洗這個澡？
She has got so much going on.
她發生了很多事情。
We have only two options.
我們只有兩個選擇。
We have Friday.
我們有星期五。
Well, that's just two days away.
嗯，只剩兩天了。
What is the other option?
還有什麼選擇？
Yesterday.
昨天。
Well, if we make it yesterday, woo-hoo,
好吧，如果我們昨天成功了，嗚呼，
we're done.
我們完成了。
Oh, God, Phoebe, this is impossible.
哦，上帝，菲比，這是不可能的。
We can't do this by Friday.
我們不能在星期五之前做到這一點。
We have to find a place.
我們得找個地方。
We have to invite people.
我們必須邀請人們。
We have to get food.
我們必須得到食物。
There's just too much to do.
有太多事情要做。
It's impossible.
這是不可能的。
We can't do it.
我們做不到。
We cannot do it.
Calm down.
冷靜下來。
Okay.
好的。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
You're right.
你說得對。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Just calm down, woman.
冷靜點，女人。
I already did.
我已經這麼做了。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
I need to calm down a little.
我需要冷靜一下。
Okay.
好的。
Okay, I think we can do this if
好的，我想我們可以這樣做，如果
we just get organized, all right?
我們只是組織起來，好嗎？
We have two days to plan this party.
我們有兩天時間來規劃這次聚會。
We just need to make fast decisions.
我們只需要快速做出決定。
Okay.
好的。
Where are we going to have it?
我們要去哪裡得到它？
Here.
這裡。
What time?
什麼時候？
Four o'clock.
四點鐘。
Food?
食物？
Finger sandwiches and tea.
手指三明治和茶。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
Very Monica.
非常莫妮卡。
And chili.
還有辣椒。
Ah, you went one too far.
啊，你太過分了。
Flowers or balloons?
鮮花還是氣球？
Both.
兩個都。
We're paying for this, you know.
我們正在為此付出代價，你知道。
Neither.
兩者都不。
Okay.
好的。
What should we do for the theme?
我們應該為主題做什麼？
Lusts of the flesh.
肉體的情慾。
What?
什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Cowboy theme?
牛仔主題？
Hey.
嘿。
You know, I'm really glad we decided not
你知道，我真的很高興我們決定不這麼做
to sleep together before the wedding.
婚禮前一起睡。
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
Me too.
我也是。
You know, I was thinking, if we had
你知道，我在想，如果我們有
a big fight and we broke up for
一場大吵，我們分手了
a few hours...
幾個小時...
Yeah?
是的？
Technically, we could have sex again.
從技術上講，我們可以再次發生性行為。
What do you think?
你怎麼認為？
Bossy and domineering?
霸道又霸道？
The wedding is off.
婚禮取消了。
Sloppy and immature.
草率且不成熟。
That's me.
這就是我。
Come on.
快點。
My cousin Cassie's in the guest room.
我表哥卡西在客房。
We're supposed to have lunch.
我們該吃午餐了。
Well, get rid of her, obsessive and shrill.
好吧，擺脫她吧，她固執又尖銳。
Shrill?
尖銳？
The wedding is back on.
婚禮又開始了。
I thought I heard voices.
我以為我聽到聲音了。
You must be Chandler.
你一定是錢德勒。
Hi.
你好。
Nice to meet you.
很高興見到你。
Nice to meet you, too.
我也很高興見到你。
So, you ready to go?
那麼，你準備好出發了嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Chandler?
錢德勒？
I'll be right with you.
我馬上就和你在一起。
Cassie needs to stay at your place.
卡西需要留在你的地方。
Why?
為什麼？
Because pervy Perverson over here can't stop staring
因為這裡的變態 Perverson 無法停止凝視
at her.
對她。
What?
什麼？
Chandler, she's our cousin.
錢德，她是我們的表妹。
I was not staring at her, okay?
我沒有盯著她看，好嗎？
I was just listening intently.
我只是專心地聽著。
It's called being a good conversationalist.
這就是所謂的成為一個善於交談的人。
Watch.
手錶。
Say something.
說些什麼。
You were staring about eight inches south of
你凝視著南方約八吋的地方
there.
那裡。
Fine.
美好的。
She can stay at my place.
她可以住在我家。
By the way, what does Cassie even look
順便問一下，卡西到底長啥樣？
like now?
像現在一樣？
She looks exactly like Aunt Marilyn.
她看起來和瑪麗蓮阿姨一模一樣。
Hmm.
唔。
So, Aunt Marilyn, is she coming to the
那麼，瑪麗蓮阿姨，她會來嗎？
wedding?
婚禮？
Wafer thin ice.
薄冰晶圓。
Hey, I'm back.
嘿，我回來了。
Hi, Joey.
嗨，喬伊。
So, will I be reading the same scene
那麼，我會讀到同樣的場景嗎？
again?
再一次？
Actually, I tried to call you.
事實上，我試著打電話給你。
You didn't need to come down here today.
你今天不需要來這裡。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
You know, I would have been perfect for
你知道，我本來是完美的
this part, but whatever.
這部分，但無論如何。
Thanks for making a bad decision and ruining
感謝你做出了錯誤的決定並毀了
your movie.
你的電影。
Good day.
再會。
Look, Joey, you didn't need to come down
聽著，喬伊，你不需要下來
because the director saw your tape from yesterday
因為導演看了你昨天的錄影帶
and loved it.
並喜歡它。
And scene.
還有場景。
Huh?
啊？
Isn't that fun?
這不是很有趣嗎？
We did a little improv there, yeah.
我們在那裡做了一些改進，是的。
Okay.
好的。
So, you were saying?
那麼，你是說？
Well, the director thinks you're really right for
嗯，導演認為你真的很適合
the part and wants to meet you tomorrow.
部分並希望明天與您見面。
Wow, sure.
哇，當然。
That's great.
那太棒了。
Oh, and your agent said you're okay with
哦，你的經紀人說你同意
the nudity.
裸體。
Yeah, yeah, sure.
是的，是的，當然。
Just as long as it's handled tastefully and
只要處理得有品味
that barn is not too cold.
那個穀倉不太冷。
Okay, well, there's one more thing.
好吧，還有一件事。
It's really important to the director that everything
對導演來說，一切都非常重要
in this movie is authentic.
這部電影是真實的。
Yeah.
是的。
And so, in your love scene with Sarah,
所以，在你和莎拉的愛情場景中，
she talks about how she's never seen a
她談到她從未見過
naked man who wasn't Jewish.
裸體男人不是猶太人。
So...
所以...
So, what?
所以呢？
So, uh, well, the director is insisting that
所以，呃，導演堅持認為
whoever played that part be authentically, uh, anatomically
無論誰扮演這個角色，都應該是真實的，呃，解剖學上的
not Jewish.
不是猶太人。
You get what I'm saying?
你明白我在說什麼嗎？
Yes.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
No, what?
不，什麼？
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would
此時的義大利天主教移民會
not be...
不是...
Bar Mitzvahed?
成年禮酒吧？
Think 13 years earlier, lose the rabbi at
想想13年前，失去拉比
a scalpel.
一把手術刀。
Oh.
哦。
So, to get this part, you can't be...
所以，要獲得這部分，你不能...
No.
不。
But you are?
但你是嗎？
Yep.
是的。
But you told him you weren't.
但你告訴他你不是。
That's right.
這是正確的。
Wow, wow.
哇，哇。
And it's definitely all gone.
而這一切肯定都消失了。
There's nothing there to work with.
那裡沒有什麼可以合作的。
What were you thinking?
你在想什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I really want this part.
我真的很想要這個部分。
You know, and they tell you, no matter
你知道，他們告訴你，無論如何
what you get asked during an audition, you
試鏡時你會被問到什麼
say yes.
說是的。
Like, if they want you to ride a
就像，如果他們想讓你騎
horse, you tell them you can, and you
馬，你告訴他們你可以，然後你
just figure out how to do it later.
稍後再想辦法怎麼做。
Joey, this is not like learning to ride
喬伊，這不像學騎車
a horse.
一匹馬。
This is like learning to grow a turtleneck.
這就像學習長高領毛衣一樣。
I know, I know, I know, okay?
我知道，我知道，我知道，好嗎？
And apparently tomorrow, when I go in to
顯然明天，當我進去時
meet the director, I have to take off
見了導演，我要起飛了
my clothes so that they can see what
我的衣服讓他們可以看到什麼
my body looks like.
我的身體看起來像。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What are you gonna do?
你要做什麼？
I just have to call my agent and
我只需要打電話給我的經紀人
tell her I can't do the part.
告訴她我不能勝任這個角色。
Unless...
除非...
Unless what?
除非什麼？
Well, this may sound crazy, but there may
嗯，這可能聽起來很瘋狂，但可能有
be something that we could fashion.
成為我們可以時尚的東西。
Like what?
比如什麼？
Well, I'm not sure yet, but, um, off
好吧，我還不確定，但是，嗯，關閉
the top of my head, I'm thinking double
我的頭頂在思考雙重問題
-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
雙面膠帶和某種午餐肉。
Hey, I've got a great idea for party
嘿，我有一個關於聚會的好主意
favors for the shower.
淋浴的好處。
Okay, we get some mahogany boxes and carve
好的，我們拿一些桃花心木盒子來雕刻
everyone's names in them, and then inside is
每個人的名字都在裡面，然後裡面是
each person's individual birthstone.
每個人的生日石。
Okay.
好的。
All right, you take care of that.
好吧，你照顧好這個。
And meanwhile, the party is tomorrow and we
同時，派對就在明天，我們
still don't have a guest list.
仍然沒有客人名單。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
Well, okay, who do we know that's coming?
好吧，我們知道誰會來？
Me.
我。
Are you?
你是？
Hey.
嘿。
Hi, what's up, Mom?
嗨，媽媽，怎麼了？
Well, I'm trying to make something for Joey.
嗯，我正在努力為喬伊做點什麼。
Do you mind if I raid your fridge?
你介意我搜尋你的冰箱嗎？
Do you have that?
你有那個嗎？
All right.
好的。
Turkey?
火雞？
That won't work.
那是行不通的。
Cheese?
起司？
That won't work.
那是行不通的。
Olive loaf?
橄欖麵包？
I hope that won't work.
我希望這不會起作用。
Are you making him a sandwich?
你會幫他做三明治嗎？
No, it's, um, more like a wrap.
不，它，呃，更像是一個包裹。
Okay, so, um, I'm gonna go, guys, and
好吧，所以，嗯，我要走了，夥計們，然後
she can get back to deciding on what
她可以回去決定要做什麼
to get me for a present.
給我送禮物。
We have to get her a present?
我們得送她禮物嗎？
Okay, look.
好吧，看一下。
Look at what I got.
看看我得到了什麼。
It's her address book.
這是她的通訊錄。
We have a guest list.
我們有一份賓客名單。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, my God, you're amazing.
哦，天哪，你太棒了。
Did you just pull that out of her
你剛剛是不是把這個從她身上拉出來了？
purse?
錢包？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
And a little seed money for the potty.
還有一點用來買便盆的種子錢。
All right.
好的。
Cassie?
卡西？
Hey, Rob.
嘿，羅布。
Hi.
你好。
It's been so long.
已經過去這麼久了。
Last time I saw you, you were setting
上次我見到你時，你正在設定
up your tent in line to see Return
搭起帳篷排隊等待返回
of the Jedi.
絕地武士。
Oh, that's right.
哦，是這樣。
So you did see me that day because
所以那天你確實看到了我，因為
it seems like you didn't.
看來你沒有。
Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
哦，是的，對此感到抱歉。
It's okay.
沒關係。
Come on in.
進來吧。
Thanks for letting me stay here.
謝謝你讓我留在這裡。
I mean, Monica's place was nice, but her
我是說，莫妮卡的地方很好，但她
fiancé sure stares a lot.
未婚夫肯定常常盯著看。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You do a great Chandler.
你演了一個很棒的錢德勒。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Yeah, I have the knack for impressions.
是的，我有印象的訣竅。
Well, maybe after we get reacquainted, you could
好吧，也許當我們重新熟悉之後，你可以
do me.
做我吧。
Yeah, no!
是的，不！
Cassie, how you doing on that...
卡西，你在這方面做得怎麼樣......
hot dog?
熱狗？
I'm all done.
我都完成了。
Thank God.
感謝上帝。
I guess the last time we really hung
我想我們上次真的掛了
out was when our parents rented that beach
當我們的父母租用那個海灘時
house together.
一起住。
Oh, right, right.
哦，對了，對了。
Oh, remember the time I pinned you down
噢，還記得我把你壓倒的那次嗎
and tickled you until you cried?
逗你癢癢直到你哭？
We're probably too old to do that now.
我們現在可能已經太老了，無法做到這一點。
I'll always remember that summer because it's when
我永遠記得那個夏天，因為那時
I got all these freckles.
我身上長滿了這些雀斑。
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
嗯嗯嗯嗯。
And I'll always remember that summer because that's
我會永遠記得那個夏天，因為那是
when I realized that we are related.
當我意識到我們是有血緣關係的時候。
You know, we're not just two random people
你知道，我們不只是兩個隨機的人
thrown together.
扔在一起。
We share genetic material.
我們共享遺傳物質。
Took you that long to figure it out,
你花了那麼長時間才弄清楚
huh?
嗯？
I'm a little slow.
我有點慢。
Just as our children would be.
就像我們的孩子一樣。
Hi.
你好。
Frank, how are you?
弗蘭克，你好嗎？
Good.
好的。
Hi, thanks for coming.
你好，謝謝你的光臨。
Oh, thank you.
哦，謝謝。
Thank you.
謝謝。
No?
不？
All right.
好的。
Oh, so nice to see you.
哦，很高興見到你。
You, too.
你也是。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, Rach.
嘿，瑞秋。
Yeah?
是的？
Who the hell are all these people?
這些人到底是誰？
No, I don't know.
不，我不知道。
I called all the people in Monica's phone
我打了電話給莫妮卡手機裡的所有人
book and these are the only ones that
書，這些是唯一的
could show up on 24 hours' notice.
可以提前 24 小時通知出現。
Huh.
呵呵。
You know, there's another word for people like
你知道，還有另一個詞可以形容這樣的人
that.
那。
Losers.
失敗者。
Hi, I'm Rachel.
嗨，我是雷切爾。
This is Phoebe.
這是菲比。
I'm the maid of honor.
我是伴娘
How do you know Monica?
你怎麼認識莫妮卡的？
I was her accountant four years ago.
四年前我是她的會計師。
Oh.
哦。
I'm very interested to find out who's been
我很有興趣知道誰去過
doing her taxes the last four years.
過去四年報稅。
That's great.
那太棒了。
So what time is Monica supposed to get
那麼莫妮卡應該幾點到
here?
這裡？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Excuse us.
對不起。
You didn't tell her to come?
你沒有叫她來嗎？
You were supposed to tell her.
你應該告訴她的。
No, I wasn't.
不，我不是。
You were supposed to tell her to come
你應該告訴她來
and I was supposed to bring the cake.
我本來應該要帶蛋糕的。
Fine, I'll go call her.
好吧，我去打電話給她。
Yes, and please tell her to bring a
是的，請告訴她帶一個
cake.
蛋糕。
Okay, we have a lot of options here.
好的，我們這裡有很多選擇。
A number of prototypes for you to try
多個原型供您嘗試
on.
在。
Oh.
哦。
Those look great.
那些看起來很棒。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap.
好吧，這是蘑菇帽。
This one is made of bologna.
這是由博洛尼亞製成的。
And the toothpicks?
還有牙籤？
Oh, just until the glue dries.
哦，直到膠水乾了。
Thank God.
感謝上帝。
Now these are more realistic, but perishable.
現在這些比較現實，但也容易消逝。
Okay.
好的。
Over here, we have pink suede, which is
在這裡，我們有粉紅色麂皮，這是
nice.
好的。
But if it gets wet, then you know,
但如果它弄濕了，那你知道，
it's going to shrink.
它會縮小。
Maybe we just take that one away.
也許我們只是把那個拿走。
I also did a little something in fur,
我還用皮草做了一些東西，
but that's really just for me.
但這確實只適合我。
So, why don't you go into your room
那麼，為什麼不進你的房間呢？
and try these on and we'll see if
試穿一下，看看是否
we'll get a better idea of what's going
我們會更瞭解正在發生的事情
to work.
去工作。
Thanks.
謝謝。
You are such a good friend, and this
你真是個好朋友，而且這個
is so weird.
太奇怪了。
Okay, the taffy's too sticky.
好吧，太妃糖太黏了。
I was afraid of that.
我很害怕。
Ow!
噢！
Toothpick?
牙籤？
Yeah.
是的。
What are you trying on now?
你現在在嘗試什麼？
The fruit roll-up.
水果卷。
And?
和？
Delicious.
可口的。
Joey?
喬伊？
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下。
We have a winner.
我們有一個贏家。
What?
什麼？
Which one?
哪一個？
The silly putty.
愚蠢的膩子。
Not so silly anymore.
不再那麼傻了。
She's your cousin.
她是你的表弟。
If she knew what was going on in
如果她知道裡面發生了什麼
your head, she'd think you were sick.
你的頭，她會認為你有病。
Or would she?
或者她會嗎？
Let's back up for a second.
讓我們先回顧一下。
She was the one who suggested opening a
她是建議開設一家
bottle of wine.
一瓶酒。
She was the one who turned down the
她是那個拒絕的人
lights.
燈。
She was the one that wanted to rent
她是那個想租的人
Logan's Run, the sexiest movie ever.
《洛根逃亡》，有史以來最性感的電影。
Oh, I know that book.
哦，我知道那本書。
Forget it.
忘了它。
I want it.
我要它。
She wants it.
她想要它。
I'm going in.
我要進去了。
Say something clever.
說點聰明的吧。
Okay, it doesn't have to be clever.
好吧，不一定要聰明。
It just has to be words.
它只是必須是言語。
Say some words.
說幾句話。
Any words will do.
任何言語都可以。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
This is the longest that anyone has not
這是迄今為止最長的一次
talked ever.
曾經談過。
There is nothing you can say to make
沒有什麼是你可以說的
this worse.
這更糟。
So just say something.
所以就說點什麼吧。
I haven't had sex in a very long
我已經很久沒有做愛了
time.
時間。
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
是啊，你真的不該說什麼。
Phoebe, Rachel, it's Monica.
菲比，瑞秋，我是莫妮卡。
I wonder what you could possibly need me
我想知道你可能需要我什麼
for in such short notice.
因為在這麼短的時間內。
Oh.
哦。
Monica, we are so sorry.
莫妮卡，我們很抱歉。
For what?
為了什麼？
Well, first, for forgetting to throw you a
好吧，首先，因為忘記給你扔一個
bridal shower.
新娘送禮會。
And then for forgetting to invite you to
然後忘記邀請你了
it.
它。
You already had it?
你已經擁有了嗎？
Yeah, well, we called everyone in your phone
是的，好吧，我們給你手機裡的每個人都打了電話
book and a bunch of people came, but
書和一群人來了，但是
it took us so long to get you
我們花了很長時間才找到你
here that they had to leave.
他們不得不離開這裡。
We wanted to throw you a big surprise
我們想給你一個大驚喜
and a great shower and now you don't
和一個很棒的淋浴，但現在你不需要了
have either.
都有。
We ruined everything.
我們毀了一切。
Oh, no, wait a minute, that's not true.
哦，不，等一下，這不是真的。
No, what you did, it was really sweet.
不，你所做的，真的很甜蜜。
And it kind of works out for the
這對
best.
最好的。
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思？
Well, now I get to spend my shower
好吧，現在我要洗澡了
with the only people I really love.
和我唯一真正愛的人在一起。
I mean, and I get all those presents
我是說，我收到了所有這些禮物
without having to talk to a bunch of
無需與一群人交談
people I don't even like.
我甚至不喜歡的人。
Surprise!
驚喜！
And what's cool is the character is from
最酷的是這個角色來自
Naples, right?
那不勒斯，對嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
My whole family's from Naples.
我全家都來自那不勒斯。
That's great.
那太棒了。
Okay, well, I've heard everything I need to
好吧，我已經聽到我需要的一切
hear.
聽到。
We just need to, uh...
我們只需要，呃...
Leslie?
萊斯利？
Joey, this is the awkward part.
喬伊，這是尷尬的部分。
Oh, hey, right.
哦，嘿，對了。
Not a problem.
不是問題。
I totally understand.
我完全明白。
You need to, you know, make sure I
你需要，你知道，確保我
don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
沒有任何可怕的疤痕或紋身。
Don't you worry.
別擔心。
I have nothing to hide.
我沒有什麼好隱瞞的。
So there you go.
所以就這樣吧。
Well, that's me.
嗯，那就是我。
100% natural.
100% 天然。
I tell you, that has never happened before.
我告訴你，以前從未發生過這種情況。
Cassie, are you finding everything okay in there?
卡西，你發現裡面一切都好嗎？
Yeah, thank you so much for letting me
是的，非常感謝你讓我
stay here.
留在這裡。
Oh, it's no problem.
哦，沒問題。
What?
什麼？
Say something.
說些什麼。
Say anything.
說什麼都行。
Ask her out.
請她出去。
She's not your cousin.
她不是你的表弟。